And so now we have to realize it has a very big symbol
Supraskime, kokią svarbą turi
that we all have gathered to this great city of Rome.
šis mūsų susibūrimas didingame Romos mieste.
As I said, Europe is the liver.
Kaip sakiau, Europa yra kepenys.
That means all the attention is in Europe.
Tai reiškia, jog Europa atsakinga už dėmesį.
But the attention, if does not have the heart
Tačiau be širdies dėmesys yra
it is absolutely not integrated, nor it is enlightened.
atsiskyręs ir nenušvitęs.
But when the heart is sleeping how to bring heart to the attention?
O kaip sujungti širdį su dėmesiu, jei širdis miega?
But some tricks here and there played so well
Tačiau suveikė kelios pasitelktos gudrybės,
that the heart, like a lion, leaped and we are here.
ir širdis liuoktelėjo tarsi liūtas – taip mes atsidūrėme čia.
The joy of all the Sahaja Yogis is now going to fill the attention
Sahadža jogų džiaugsmas pripildys dėmesį,
and new powers will be developed for all of you
tada jūs visi įgysite naujų galių
and you will all feel responsible for spreading Sahaja Yoga.
ir jausitės atsakingi už Sahadža jogos sklaidą.
It has to happen.
Tai turi įvykti.
Thus we realize that through effort,
Taip atrandame, jog stengdamiesi
we all can achieve the impossible.
galime pasiekti neįmanomą.
Brahmarandra is the heart, is the heart chakra.
„Brahmarandra“ [momenėlio centras] yra širdis, širdies čakra.
And unless and until there is heart into our work we are not enlightened people.
Ir kol mumyse teveikia širdis, nesame nušvitę.
All our efforts will be futile.
Visos mūsų pastangos bergždžios.
Without the attention the heart is useless.
Širdis yra bevertė be dėmesio.
So this beautiful meeting that has taken place is writing in the skies
Taigi šis susitikimas yra tarsi rašymas danguje
with the warmth of the heart and light of the attention,
širdies šiluma ir dėmesio šviesa,
that the glorious days have come
jog išaušo palaimintos dienos
for us to enjoy our complete freedom,
mums mėgautis visiška laisve,
freedom from all our enemies, all our ignorance.
išsivadavus iš priešų ir nepažinimo tamsos.